have you ever wondered that how can you
replace sin x by simply X for smaller
values of X well those zoman expansion
might know that you can just ignore the
higher powers of X but here is a visual
proof for it if you plot the function
sinx and the function y = x then you can
see that in this region both of these
curves almost overlap each other that
means that no matter what input you give
in this region the output of both of
these functions is almost equal to each
other and you can do the same thing for
more functions like tangent X sin
inverse X tangent inverse X and even sin
hyperbolic X and tangent hyperbolic X
behaves the same if you're interested in
such science and math video subscribe
for more